(Amy:)-What?
-Poor Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)I hate to pile on the bad news,
but I just got a raise.
(Howard:)My God, Bernie, what happened?
(Bernadette:)Well, let's just say the next time
you move a dozen vials
(Bernadette:)of raccoon virus to the fridge,
make two trips.
(Howard:)You're sure you're okay?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, it's just a precaution.
If there was a problem,
(Bernadette:)I'd be throwing up
out of my eyeballs by now.
(Bernadette:)-Sorry I messed up our date.
-No, don't worry about it.
(Howard:)I brought the date here.
(Howard:)Guys, come on in.
(Bernadette:)What's all this?
(Howard:)Well, tonight is the anniversary
of our first date,
(Howard:)and I wanted to celebrate it
by writing a song for you.
(Bernadette:)Howie.
Sheldon, get over hers!
(Sheldon:)She might be contagious.
(Sheldon:)Don't you think I'm having
a rough enough day?
Sheldon!